Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Not the headline I was hoping for
a week before the election.
Nobody's that squeaky-clean.
We'll find something to use against him.
You've never met Jonathan Kent.
Mr. Luthor?
- We need to get you out of here.
- What's going on?
There's been a bomb threat.
We need to evacuate.
- A bomb?
- My security didn't alert me about this.
Lex?
You always gotta do things
the hard way, don't you?
Let me guess, you're not a cop.
Not anymore.
Stop him.
At the risk of stating the obvious...
...but whatever game
you think you're playing...
...you just lost.
If you're trying the hard-wire,
good luck.
I cut it a half-hour ago. Right around
the time I set up the wireless scrambler.
Looks like the game is just starting.
- What do you want?
- I'll give you a hint.
It's big...
... metallic,
it came from outer space.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Sure you do.
I want that ship
that landed in the meteor shower.
Or that room is gonna be your coffin,
Luthor.
Okay, so when you said,
"Let's get together and study" ...
...you actually meant study.
Kiss me.
Clark, what am I, your cousin?
Really kiss me.
I gotta go. I don't wanna miss class.
Wouldn't want you
to be late for class.
- Lana, come on.
- Clark, what is it?
When we kiss, when we really kiss...
...I can feel how much you want me.
Why can't we just be together?
It's complicated.
It shouldn't be.
Not when you love somebody.
Lana, wait.
What is this?
Nothing.
Did you get this from Lex?
We've been researching it together
for the last couple of weeks.
Why would you keep this from me?
Because, Clark...
...every time I try to bring up the ship
I saw, you change the subject.
Just don't think there's any point
in dwelling on it.
I saw what came out of that ship.
I watched them kill
all those police officers.
I almost died,
and all you can say to me is:
"There's no point in dwelling on it"?
I turned to Lex because he wants
to find out the truth...
...not avoid it.
A spaceship?
Have you tried the amusement park?
They have one you can ride for a dollar.
I know you took that ship
after the meteor shower, Luthor.
You do realize
how crazy you sound right now.
Does this look crazy to you?
I was there.
I was part of the Sheriff's Response
Team that got wiped out.
I was under my cruiser, half dead.
I saw you roll up
with your equipment and men.
You didn 't even bother to see
if anybody was still alive.
All you cared about
was hauling that ship away.
Sorry, but I still don't know
what you're talking about.
You're going to make a great politician,
Luthor.
You almost sound like you believe
your own lies.
You want to make it to Election Day?
- Tell me what I want to know.
- Or what?
I had this room designed after that
little incident at the missile silo.
These walls can withstand
a nuclear blast. You'll never get in here.
And you'll never get out.
Your security team's tied up
in the basement.
Your wireless system 's blocked.
You won 't be sending up
any smoke signals for help.
Looks like we have ourselves
a stalemate.
Well, I guess I'll have to find
a way to break it.
Lana's helping Lex
study the black ship?
She's got a detailed drawing from
LuthorCorp.
She's been lying to me for weeks.
Well, you haven't exactly been honest
with her either, Clark.
Sometimes the truth isn't easy to share
with the one you love.
Especially if you think it might hurt.
Everything was so perfect with Lana
when I lost my abilities.
Now that I have them back,
all I do is lie to her.
About the ship, about why l...
I just wish I could tell her.
I'm not saying you should,
but Pete found out, and Chloe...
...and they accepted you
for who you are.
- Yeah. I'm an alien.
- No, as their friend.
Whom they love very much no matter
what star you were born under.
Just not sure Lana's gonna feel
the same way.
Then maybe she's not the one
you were meant to be with.
Mom, I can't imagine
ever loving anyone else.
Hey, Smallville, Mrs. Kent.
Have you guys seen the future senator?
It's crunch time.
- We've got some billionaire butt to kick.
- I think he's in the barn, Lois.
Salt of the earth. Voters love that.
Turn that frown upside down, Skippy.
All right? Unhappy family members
reflect badly at the polls.
I'm looking forward to this campaign
being over.
This isn't about numbers,
demographics or projections.
It's about giving everybody the chance
to live a life with dignity.
Whether they have a dollar in the bank,
or a million.
That's why I got involved in the senate
race and that's why I intend to win.
Regardless of my opponent's checkbook,
I don't care how big it is.
Listen, if you need
any more comment...
...call my campaign manager,
Lois Lane.
She'll talk to you, all right? Thanks.
You're getting very smooth
with the interviews.
I've had a lot of practice. I feel like
I got a phone growing out of my ear.
Well, you're doing great.
Homestretch, senator.
I'm not the senator,
I haven't won anything yet.
Well, you will when I'm done.
Here we are. This is what we're doing.
Print ads in all the papers,
radio spots across the dial...
...billboards littering the interstate
like roadkill...
...and the nail that is going to
close the coffin...
...on our bald-headed wannabe's
campaign...
...the heartland message...
...on every TV station across Kansas
from now until Election Day.
Well, it sounds like somebody I know
needs a raise.
Technically,
you'd have to start paying me first.
Lois, this is all really fantastic,
but how can we afford it?
You know what,
don't even bother with the details.
You just need to shake hands
and kiss babies, all right?
Let's talk about your schedule
from now till Election Day.
- You're gonna be one busy guy.
- Yeah.
I know how he feels about Lex,
but what am I supposed to do, Chloe?
It's like there's this part of clark
that just shuts down...
...anytime I start talking about
the meteors or what I saw.
Okay, let me just call you back
in a second, all right?
I'm sorry, officer,
I know I was driving a little bit fast.
That's the least of your problems,
Miss Lang.
What are you doing?
Shut your mouth.
Lana?
- Let her go.
- Lex?
I said, let her go.
Remember that stalemate
you were talking about, Luthor?
- Lex, why are they doing this?
- Yeah, Lex, why all the fuss?
Lana, they're looking for a spaceship.
- What spaceship?
- Is everybody stupid around here?
Tell us where it is
and all this is over.
She doesn't know anything.
Yeah, well, she was there
when it crashed.
And I know you two have been
spending an awful lot of time together.
So get your ass out here now
or you'll be talking to yourself.
I guess you're not as important
after all.
Step out.
Check him.
Don't worry, Lana.
I'm not gonna let this psycho hurt you.
You think you can stop me, Luthor?
- You all right? You hurt?
- No, I'm okay.
I warned you knowing about that ship
could be dangerous.
Lex.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Lex.
Oh, my God.
Come on, Bob,
you can do better than this.
I know it's 30 seconds
smack in the middle of prime time...
...that's why it's called "prime."
Drop 10 grand and I promise you,
I will get you a personal invitation...
...to Senator Kent's election party.
I'll save you a dance. Thanks, Bob.
Wow, prime time.
That must have cost a bit, huh?
Feminine wiles.
Bob's got a crush on me.
Parts of me.
He let me have it for next to nothing.
I wonder if all you nice people
wouldn't mind...
...giving Miss Lane and I
a few minutes?
Why don't you get yourself
a cup of coffee.
Thank you.
Wow, "Miss Lane."
I'm feeling all professional.
You've really grown into your role
well here, Lois.
Like the way you managed
to get all this last-minute publicity.
That's very impressive.
Thanks, boss.
It also must be very expensive.
I told you not to bother with that,
I've got it covered.
Yeah, you see, that's my problem.
I'm crunching the numbers,
they don't seem to add up, Lois.
We're spending more than we have.
A lot more.
- Well, I just called in a few favors.
- Lois.
I appreciate everything you're doing,
I really do.
But you've got to stop
sidestepping my question.
Where's the money coming from?
Lionel Luthor.
I didn't have a choice.
The well ran dry,
and without Lionel's backing...
...our campaign would have folded
weeks ago.
It was the right thing to do.
We actually have a chance
to win this thing now.
What is the point
if the devil owns your soul?
It's not like that.
He doesn't want anything from you.
This is about Lex.
Lionel's gonna do anything he can
to stop Lex from becoming senator.
I'm sure that that's true.
But you don't know Lionel like I do.
He doesn't give anyone
anything for free. There's always a price.
I'm the one that's
gonna have to pay it.
Clark...
...can you put on the brakes
before you tornado my homework?
I'm sorry.
All right, Dostoyevsky's Idiot isn't
gonna get any smarter, so come on...
...Miss Sullivan's advice column
is open for letters.
Lana and I had another fight.
I know, she called me
right after the big blowout.
What did she say?
Just the headlines: Spaceship, boyfriend
that always changes the subject...
...forced to turn to
everyone's favorite villain.
How long has she been
working on this?
I don't know, actually.
This is the first I've ever heard of it.
You have to find out
how long they've been working together.
Are you asking me to spy on Lana?
- It's very important.
- I understand, and you're my friend...
...but so is Lana, and there is no way
I'm getting in the middle of this.
Is that Lana?
Hello? Yes, this is Chloe Sullivan.
Where?
No. No, she hasn't been back
to the dorm at all.
Yeah, I will, I will. Thank you.
What happened?
That was the Smallville
Sheriff's Department.
Something wrong?
They found Lana's car
abandoned on the side of the road.
Start a perimeter search. See if you
can find anything out in that field.
Sheriff?
Mr. Kent, what did you do,
drop out of the sky?
- Where's Lana?
- That's what we're trying to find out.
- When was the last time you saw her?
- Couple of hours ago.
- We had a fight.
- Well, that's what people in love do...
...then they make up...
...which I aim to give you
and Miss Lang the chance to do.
We found her purse, everything's in it.
And the car speaks for itself.
I'd peg this as a kidnapping
but there's no sign of a struggle...
...which suggests she either knew
her assailant or was caught off-guard.
Either way, we'll go over
every inch of the scene...
...until we dust off
something useful...
Sheriff.
It's a GPS.
Someone must have been
following her.
How in the Sam Spade
did you know where to find this?
- Just a hunch.
- You got an awful lot of those.
I've said it before, but I could use
a man like you on the force...
...instead of some of these hayseeds.
There's a serial number on here,
"511 GKL97."
So I think maybe...
Sheriff.
We got a silent alarm
from up at the Luthor mansion.
- Harris is checking it out.
- Harris, what's your situation?
All clear, sheriff.
Looks like it was a false alarm.
Okay, keep searching the perimeter.
You get anything,
you get me on the horn.
Getting a little warm in there?
I hacked into the climate controls.
Should hit about a buck thirty
in half an hour.
Give me a yell
when you're medium rare.
By the way, how's that bullet feel?
I know I got you.
- I can't stop it.
- It's okay.
They'll be here soon.
- Who?
- The police.
Barney Fife out there
was using a scrambler...
...to block the wireless backup alarm.
That's what you were shooting at.
If we were at the fair,
I would have won you a stuffed giraffe.
I would've liked that a lot more than
you getting shot trying to protect me.
I was just trying to get us
back into the panic room.
I know what you did, Lex.
Thank you.
Lana...
...I'm sorry
that you got sucked into this.
Why didn't you just tell them
where the spaceship was?
This isn't worth your life.
I can't tell them the truth...
...because they'd kill both of us.
Mr. Luthor?
I don't think they'll get the chance.
- Sheriff, what are you doing here?
- Out for a stroll. What do you think?
I already told you
it was a false alarm.
Coming from the mansion of a billionaire
running for state senate?
Luthor manages to get himself elected,
I don't want him chewing my backside...
...for not showing up to hold his hand.
Now, where is he?
- Out, I guess. I haven't...
- Out?
You don't stand down an alarm without
talking to the primary resident, Harris.
Now get your head in the game.
Sheriff.
Flynn?
Well, ain't that a mother.
Why is this taking so long?
Well, getting past the server's firewall
and the encryption protocol takes time.
Sorry, clark, but I don't have
a super-speed mode. Get out of here.
But I am the slickest blond
you'll ever meet.
Okay, so it looks like the serial number
for the GPS you found...
...matches a unit sold
to a Gregory Flynn.
What do you got on him?
In a couple of seconds, everything.
Clark, Lana's gonna be okay.
She has you, doesn't she?
Oh, here we go. "Flynn, Gregory R."
He's a Smallville sheriff's officer.
Yeah, up until a couple of months ago.
He was put on psychiatric leave
because he was wounded...
...and his entire unit was killed during
the meteor shower.
He was there when
the spaceship landed.
- When those Kryptonians killed everyone.
- Yeah, but Flynn survived the attack.
God, seeing something like that.
I mean...
...all those people you work with,
your friends.
No wonder he had a psychotic break.
Let's go.
- Why would he kidnap Lana?
- I don't know, but she was there too.
I thought maybe if we can get
his psych workup...
...we can figure out
what it is that he's up to.
Yeah.
I can't believe Lois would take money
from Lionel behind my back.
- She has no idea what he's capable of.
- It wasn't her fault.
Martha, please.
Don't defend her to me.
I'm not.
I took the money from Lionel.
How could you do that?
Because I know how much
this means to you, Jonathan.
To be able to make
a real difference in the world...
...the way our son does everyday.
I love you so much.
I don't want you to lose
because Lex has a bigger bank account.
I promised the only people I would owe
were the people who voted for me.
Now that I've taken it, I'm no different
than any other lying politician.
You think the Farmers Association
and the Rotary Club...
...and everyone else who gave
you money won't be asking for favors?
They can ask anything that they want.
But I won't do something
I don't believe in.
Then why should it be
any different with Lionel?
Martha, you know it's not the same.
I know nothing is black or white,
especially in politics.
If you win this election...
...you'll be able to help so many people
who desperately need it.
Please, don't let your pride
get in the way.
How many more people
have to die for this?
As many as it takes.
Luthor can 't last much longer in there.
He'll bleed out
if he doesn 't open that door.
Lex. Hey, hey, come on. Wake up.
You're in shock.
Stay conscious or else
you might die. Okay?
All right.
Okay, well, tell me something.
- What?
- Anything. Just keep talking, okay?
You think I'd look better with hair?
I don't know.
I've never thought about it.
Oh, I have.
I've thought about a lot of things.
Clark has really nice hair.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess he does.
- Does he know?
- That he has nice hair?
How lucky he is.
I had a dream once, Lana.
About how different things could be.
It was Christmas.
Clark and I were friends again.
Well, that sounds really nice.
You were in my dream too.
I was?
You were the best part about it.
Lex. Lex, we have
to get you out of here, all right?
Just give them what they want.
I can't tell them where it is.
This spaceship isn't gonna make
any difference if you're dead.
I can't tell them where it is
because I honestly don't know.
What?
One minute it was there
and the next...
Nothing but static on the security
cameras and an empty warehouse.
I'm sorry.
How long have you known this?
A few weeks.
Lex, how could you have lied
to me this entire time?
Because I didn't know
how to tell you the truth, Lana.
Your life, mine.
They've both been affected
so much by these meteors.
That ship was our one chance
to understand why.
I was hoping
that I might find it again before...
I should have been honest with you.
Lex?
Lex. Lex. Oh, God.
Lex, Lex, please don't... Stay awake.
Lex, please. Please, wake up.
Oh, God.
I'll tell you where the ship is. But first
you have to get Lex help. He's hurt.
I've seen worse.
Call for help, and I'll tell you where it is.
That's the deal.
Well, I'm making a new deal. Take me
to the ship. Then I make the call.
Lana, don't.
All right.
Okay, this is what we're gonna do.
You're gonna wait here.
I'll double back and see if I can hack
into the visitors list to get us passes.
Then we can come back in and maybe
get right by that guy right there.
I got it.
What did you do?
Super shake.
Not bad. Not bad.
- I am not crazy.
- No one's saying that.
Then why won 't you believe me?
I saw a ship crash
in the meteor shower.
I saw what came out of it.
- Gregory...
- They hit us with some heat beams...
... from their eyes.
Took out the cars and the helicopter.
I was pinned.
I could smell something burning.
It was me.
I was burning.
Didn 't scream, didn 't make a sound
because they would've seen me.
- Who?
- Those things from the ship.
They killed everyone.
Everyone except the girl.
She got away.
- We've been over this.
- Lana.
There is no ship.
Your team was hit by a meteor.
That's what he wants you to believe!
I saw him take the ship!
I am not crazy!
Ask Lex Luthor!
He knows the truth! He has the ship!
Lex.
Clark, that's where they must be.
Damn, I wish I could do that.
Sheriff?
Lex.
Lex?
We're here.
Make the call and get Lex help.
After I see the ship.
What are you gonna do? Climb inside
and fly away? There's no way in.
Oh, we don't plan to.
You don't want to take the ship.
You want to destroy it.
That thing crashed from outer space.
Couple of pounds
of c-4 wouldn't dent it.
But it will make an awful lot of noise.
Police, fire, news crews,
they'll all come running.
And they'll see it.
Just like us. Only difference is,
you kept quiet and I told the truth.
And they sent him
to a psych ward for it.
And they wouldn't even let me see him,
his own fiancée.
People need to be warned
before more of them land.
It's the right thing to do.
Tell Sheriff Adams that.
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
It was here before. I swear it was.
Don't lie to me.
Lex. Lex! Where's Lana?
- Get him out of here!
- Tell me where she is.
Warehouse 15.
- Greg.
- Get the case.
We gotta get the case.
- The what?
- The case!
Greg. Greg...
- I got it.
- No, we gotta get out of here.
- Greg. We have to get out of here!
Come on!
- Lana.
- Clark?
What happened?
I don't know.
Lex told me where to find you.
When I got here,
you were laying on the ground.
I don't understand.
You're alive. That's all that matters.
She knows where the spaceship is.
Don't let her lie!
She's working with Luthor!
She knows everything!
What a nut.
How you doing?
Doing all right,
considering I almost got blown up.
I can't believe Lex would risk your life.
- Clark...
- He knew there was no ship in there.
Clark, it wasn't his idea.
I brought them here on my own.
- You did?
- It was my only chance to get Lex help.
You risked your life for Lex?
He did the same thing for me
back at the mansion.
Clark, if it wasn't for him,
I'd probably be dead.
Lex saved my life.
A good neighbor, a man who knows
the value of an honest day's work...
... and the responsibility of family.
- Jonathan Kent...
- What did you think?
I think the flag might have
been a bit much, don't you?
Nothing says America
like the Stars and Stripes.
Except maybe the name
Jonathan Kent.
I'm sorry I accepted Lionel's contribution
without asking you first.
- It was wrong. I shouldn't have done it.
- Lois. Lois.
He knows.
- He does?
- Yeah.
I know. Martha told me that
she's the one that accepted the money.
It's a fact you might've shared
when I was yelling at you.
Well, the decision to use it
was still mine.
Look, I think you are going to be
a great senator, Mr. Kent.
But the hard truth is you wouldn't have
a chance without Lionel's money.
No, Lois. The hard truth is...
...by taking it, I'm no longer the man
that you just saw on television.
And I'm no longer the man
you married.
That's why I've decided to pay back
Lionel Luthor every cent he loaned us.
How? Not having any green
is what put us in this hole.
I sold the back 40 this morning.
Jonathan, that land has been
in your family for generations.
Yeah, and I've never done
a thing with it, sweetheart.
I should have sold it years ago.
I was just too proud. I'm sorry.
I know it's not the whole thing,
but it's certainly a start. Here you go.
Well, I'll do everything I can
to help you.
I never doubted that, sweetie.
So, what happens in the meantime?
If you're right,
Lionel will want something from you.
I'll find out soon enough. But right now,
we have an election to win.
Absolutely.
That doesn't look like bed rest.
Yeah. I was never really good
at taking things lying down.
Well, you are a Luthor.
Yeah.
I guess I am.
Lana...
...I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about losing the ship.
Wouldn't matter. It'd still be gone.
Yeah, well, at least
you wouldn't hate me for it.
I don't hate you, Lex.
How could I after you risked your life
to save mine?
You're one of the few
good things in my life.
I hope that won't change.
Well, that depends on you.
All I ever asked for was the truth.
And that's all you'll ever get
from me from now on.
I promise.
Lana, we may not have the ship...
...but that doesn't mean
we can't keep trying to find it.
And solve all the mysteries
that go with it.
Partners?
No.
Let's try being friends.
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
The only reason Lana almost got killed
was because of Lex.
Lana can make her own decisions.
I'm not saying she can't,
but we all know Lex.
He twists everything
until you don't know what to believe.
Oh, no, Lex is a snake.
Believe me, I've seen his scales.
But he did almost die taking
a bullet for Lana.
- I saved her. Does that mean anything?
- Yeah.
You know what?
It would, if she knew about it.
The only reason Lana started
talking to Lex...
...was to learn more
about that spaceship.
If I was honest,
she never would've had to.
No, she wouldn't.
I love her so much, Chloe.
I know.
But all you're doing now
is pushing her further away.
That's not what I want.
I want us to be together
for the rest of our lives.
The only way that's ever gonna happen
is if you tell her the truth.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org